# DOUGLAS NONATO

(41) 9672-6604 http://www.douglasnonato.com https://vimeo.com/user6729671

#### Summary

Since 2008 as a Graphic Designer, I've worked in several projects by taking part of every single step of the workflow production, providing me a great experience with a 360° knowledge of what concerns Web Design, Graphic Design and Motion Design.

Looking for challenges that bring new experiences and skills, I'm always willing to discuss and share ideas, each project is an opportunity to learn something new.

#### Main Skills:

- UX and UI, leading improvements to web pages.
- Development of websites, from the scratch to its publication.
- Front-end programming
- 2D animation.

Check out my works www.douglasnonato.com

#### Skills

- Agile
- Web design
- After Effects
- Sketch
- CSS, Sass
- Wordpress
- User Interface
- Web responsive
- GitHub

- e Scrum
  - Motion Design
  - Photoshop
  - Bootstrap
  - NetBeans
  - User Experience
  - JavaScript
  - SourceTree
  - InDesign

- Kanban
- Cinema 4D
- Illustrator
- HTML, Slim, Jade
- Dreamweaver
- Microsoft Office
- Front-end
- Sublime

## Experience

#### Beauty Date Product Owner

07 / 2015 - Present

Beauty Date's flagship is the online booking, which connects customers to salons right in their phone screens, allowing them to book appointments whenever and wherever they want. The system also counts on basic management features such as customer base and reports, useful for salons of every size.

Responsibilities: • Lead new tools for product and improvements to the user experience;

- $\bullet$  Improvements based on customer's feedback;  $\bullet$  Interaction with marketing and IT team;
- Responsible for the group websites; Landing pages for new marketing campaigns;
- Front-end programming (Sass, Slim, Jade); Storyboard creation, 2D and 3D animations;
- Code reviwer;

#### Promova Promoções e Eventos Web and Motion Designer

The Promova I.D.E.I.A.S. has 19 years of history in promotional marketing, event organizations, relationship actions and endomarketing. Headquartered in Curitiba, operates at the national level with offices in Porto Alegre, Goiania, Brasilia, Rio de Janeiro.

Responsibilities: • Analysis of briefings and generation of ideas and concepts for projects; • Website Development. Layout design and front-end programming; • Video production for promotional actions of customers, project presentations, concepts, architectural spaces and making-off of internal projects; • Storyboard creation, 2D and 3D animations, video shooting and soundtrack creation; • Contact with customers.

#### QLance Senior Designer

02 / 2013 - 09 / 2013

Online platform for management of tournaments and events. Launched in 2013, the system was used by large university events.

Responsibilities: • Creation of graphic materials; • Interface development for web system; • User Experience; • Front-end programming.

## Agenda Beleza Web Designer

08 / 2012 - 02 / 2013

The Agenda Beleza is a business platform for Beauty Services. It allows users to find professionals in the beauty industry and schedule the service. In addition, companies can promote online payment in order to guarantee the customer attendance, returning confidence through a discount.

Responsibilities: • Creation of graphic materials; • Interface development for web system; • User Experience; • Front-end programming.

## Provisuale Designer

07 / 2009 - 03 / 2012

Founded in 1996, Provisuale has acted in the services sector as event organizer. Provisuale's main undertaking is Futurecom, the largest and most qualified Telecom, IT and Internet event in Latin America.

Responsibilities: • Participation on the development of visual identity of the events; • Creation and artwork of graphic materials; • Production of promotional videos; • Development of hot site. Layout and front-end programming; • Participation in the annual planning of the sector and operational planning of the events; • Development of marketing actions to events; • Experience with travel in times of events, responsible for management of outsourced personnel and monitoring of materials applications during these periods; • Contact with suppliers.

# Base Editorial Iconographer

01 / 2009 - 07 / 2009

Editorial base was established in 1995 in Curitiba, Paraná. Publisher focused on producing textbooks.

Responsibilities: • Image Search for textbooks; • Organization of images and their copyrights; • Image Compositions for illustration of content.

#### Education

Faculdades Integradas do Brasil - Unibrasil 2008 - 2012 Bachelor's of Graphic and Product Design , School of Communication

Btc English English course